Office of Publications Records UA012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Publications Records
1908 -- 2009
1960 -- 2002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Publications
UA012
22.1 Linear Feet 24 boxes
8 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into five series: Buildings and grounds; Students; Faculty and staff; Subject files; and Unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
This collection is composed of photographs, negatives, slides, and digital images of Tufts University from 1908 to 2009. Aside from photographic materials, the collection also contains newspaper clippings, brochures, publications, and press releases. The bulk of the collection consists of images of the Tufts campus as well as its students, faculty, and staff. The collection also captures many aspects of life at Tufts, such as events and locations that define the school, the social and academic life of students, and the professional life of faculty and staff. A large portion of the collection are stock images captured by professional photographers for publications and marketing purposes, although a number of snapshot-style images donated by alums, faculty, and staff are also included.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Publications is one of four departments comprising Tufts Office of Communications. This Office is responsible producing magazines, newsletters, and marketing material for Tufts University. Through design and writing the Office of Publication aims to capture and share the visual and intellectual identity of the University. The Office also offers editorial, design, and project management services for Tufts departments, and maintains external contracts with photographers and design firms.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
University Relations; Facilities; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty; Student life
- Buildings and grounds, 1908 -- 2009; 1963 -- 2002; UA012.001; 3.7 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains photographs, slides, and negatives of physical spaces associated with Tufts. The majority of the images were captured between 1967 and 2003, though some are more recent. The majority of the images are stock photographs of buildings on Tufts' Medford campus. While most shots depict the exterior of buildings, some also display interior scenes with and without students. Some images indicate a specific season, with a focus on Tufts' flora, fauna and foliage. Despite a focus on Medford facilities, the series also houses photographs of the Veterinary, Dental and Medical School campuses. Photographs of Boston are also included in this series. A number of images also show new construction and architectural renderings of planned buildings. Materials are both black and white and color.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Boston Health Sciences campus, 1980; UA012.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    This folder contains photographs of Sackler and students at New England Medical Center T stop. Date is approximate.
  - Boston scenes [1 of 3], 1990 -- 2001; UA012.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    Date range is approximate.
  - Boston scenes [2 of 3], 1976 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    Date range is approximate. Contains negatives and photographic prints.
  - Boston scenes [3 of 3], 1976; UA012.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    Date range is approximate. Contains negatives and photographic prints of Boston. A number of aerial shots are contained in this folder, as well as city scenes.
  - Carmichael Dining Hall, 1993; UA012.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    Contains photographic prints of new addition to Carmichael Hall's cafeteria.
  - Health Sciences Education Bldg., 1983 -- 1987; UA012.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    Contains photographic prints depicting Health Sciences Education Building as well as shots of people at the opening, people during planning, and photographs of architectural renderings.
  - Health Sciences Library, 1985 -- 1987; UA012.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    Contains photographic prints of people using Health Sciences Library. Interior shots only.
  - Health Sciences Library, 1995; UA012.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains 35 mm slides and photographic prints.
  - Jaharis Center, 1996 -- 2000; UA012.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains negatives and photographic prints of architectural plans and renderings. Also contained a CD case labeled Jaharis Renderings from Architectural Resources, with no CD inside. The label was kept and the case was discarded.
  - Latin Way Dormitory, 1979; UA012.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains photographic prints of construction, opening, and one architectural rendering.
  - Photographs, library, n.d., 1980 -- 1994; UA012.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains photographic prints of library interior, many include students using technology, reading, or speaking with staff members.
  - Medford campus - Aerial view, 1963 -- 1975; UA012.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate.
  - Medford Campus - Aidekman Arts Center, 1991; UA012.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains slides and photographic prints.
  - Medford Campus - Architectural detail, 1977 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains slides, negatives and photographic prints.
  - Medford Campus - Ballou Hall, slides & prints, 1984 -- 2002; UA012.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Ballou images, 1999; UA012.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate.
  - Medford Campus - Bendetson Hall, 1975 -- 2000; UA012.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides, negatives, and photographic prints.
  - Medford Campus - Buildings, 1993 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides, negatives, and photographic prints. Exterior photographs of Dowling, Braker, Ballou, and College of Engineering.
  - Medford Campus - Buildings, 1993 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Photographs of Campus Center and Packard Hall.
  - Medford Campus - Carmichael Hall, 1977 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides and photographic prints.
  - Medford Campus - Buildings, misc. dorms, etc., 1974 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains negatives and photographic prints of diverse campus buildings. Includes Curtis Hall, Gantcher, Miller Hall, Sweet Hall demolition and slides of various construction projects.
  - Medford Campus - Cabot Center, 1986 -- 1999; UA012.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Campus Center photos, 1984; UA012.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    Contains photographs of construction, groundbreaking, and completed building.
  - Medford Campus - Cannon, 1979 -- 1990; UA012.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Construction, 1980 -- 1995; UA012.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains photographic prints of Mayer campus center construction, Baronian Fieldhouse renderings, and Brown House demolition.
  - Medford Campus - Fall / foliage scenes, 1980 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Gifford House, 1977 -- 1996; UA012.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides, negatives and photographic prints. Includes watercolor rendering of house.
  - Medford Campus - Goddard Chapel, 1977 -- 1996; UA012.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides, negatives and photographic prints. Includes slides of Goddard's 100th anniversary.
  - Medford Campus - Hillel Center, 1993 -- 1994; UA012.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides, negatives and photographic prints. Includes slide of architectural rendering and prints of architectural model as well as fundraising brochure.
  - Medford Campus - Jumbo Photos, 1988 -- 1998; UA012.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Memorial Steps, 1980 -- 1998; UA012.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Olin Center, 1992 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Science and Technology Center, 1990 -- 1992; UA012.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - South Hall, 1995; UA012.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Spring, 1978 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Tisch Library inside, 1989 -- 1994; UA012.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains slides and photographic prints. Many shots pre-date Tisch addition and actually depict Wessell Library interior.
  - Medford Campus - Tisch Library outside, 1981 -- 1998; UA012.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains slides and photographic prints. Many photographs pre-date Tisch addition and actually depict exterior of Wessell Library. This folder also contained a CD from the Office of Publications with a High Resolution covershot of Tisch Library from an A & S Bulletin. The image was also said to be used on a Summer Session postcard. When an attempt was made to access the image, no file extension was included and the file was unreadable on all softwares. The CD cover is included in the folder.
  - Medford Campus - Tisch Library plans, 1992; UA012.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains negatives and photographic prints.
  - Medford Campus - West Hall, 1977 -- 1998; UA012.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides and photographic prints. Many shots pre-date Tisch addition and actually depict Wessell Library interior.
  - Medford Campus - Winter, 1990 -- 1996; UA012.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - Winter, 1977 -- 1993; UA012.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - with students, 1977 -- 1983; UA012.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Medford Campus - with students fall, 1977 -- 1993; UA012.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
    Dates are approximate. Contains slides and negatives.
  - New England Medical Center, 1995; UA012.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Sackler Center, 1985 -- 1995; UA012.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Slides from Breed - Color, 1980; UA012.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
    Contains slides of exteriors of campus buildings taken by photographer Jack Breed.
  - South Street, 1980; UA012.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Vet School - buildings, 1982 -- 1988; UA012.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
    Date is approximate. Contains photographic prints and slides of vet school buildings, including the Foster Hospital for Small Animals, the equine clinic, and aerial shots of the campus. Also contains a few prints of architectural renderings.
  - Medford Campus - Carmichael Hall, 1977 -- 1997; UA012.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
    Contains slides and photographic prints.
  - Aidekman, 1990; UA012.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    This folder contains photographs of Aidekman exterior. Date is approximate
  - Alumni House, UA012.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Alumni House
  - Anderson-Robinson, 1973; UA012.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Anderson-Robinson exterior
  - Anderson-Robinson, 1973; UA012.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Anderson-Robinson exterior. Date is approximate
  - Anderson-Robinson, 1986; UA012.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Anderson-Robinson exterior.
  - Anderson-Robinson, 1970; UA012.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Archives, 1975; UA012.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Archive interior and researchers. Date is approximate
  - Archives, 1975; UA012.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Archives, 1975; UA012.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Archives, 1975; UA012.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Ats Campus shots/Students, 1986; UA012.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Paige Hall and Memorial Steps
  - Ballou, Anderson, Fisher Arcade, 2009; UA012.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Alumni House, Bendeston, Olin, South Hall, Ballou, Anderson and Fisher Arcade
  - Ballou and signage, UA012.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou and signage
  - Ballou Hall, UA012.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou
  - Ballou Hall, UA012.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou, and corner of West Hall
  - Ballou Hall, 1990; UA012.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou. Date is approximate
  - Ballou Hall, 1980; UA012.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    This folder contains negatives of Ballou. Date is approximate
  - Ballou Hall, 1990; UA012.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Ballou Hall, 1980; UA012.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Barnum Hall/Dana Lab, 1980; UA012.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of exterior of Barnum Hall and Dana lab. Date is approximate
  - Bookstore, 1980; UA012.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of exterior of old bookstore. Date is approximate
  - Boston Aerials, UA012.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston Aerials.
  - Boston misc., UA012.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston Commons, skyline, Charles River, Half Shell and Swan Boats
  - Boston Aerials, UA012.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston skyline, boat
  - Boston/ N. End & Chinatown, 1970; UA012.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of North End and Chinatwon. Date is approximate
  - Boston Scenes, 1983; UA012.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston.
  - Boston Scenes, 1987; UA012.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston and maps.
  - Boston Scenes, 1990; UA012.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston. Date is approximate
  - Boston Skyline, 1994; UA012.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston skyline and boat
  - Boston Skyline, etc., 1980; UA012.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston skyline and boat. Date is approximate
  - Boston Skyline, Kennedy Library, 1994; UA012.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Boston skyline from Kennedy Library
  - Bowen Gate, 1989; UA012.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Bowen Gate
  - Braker Hall, 1983; UA012.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Braker hall
  - Braker Hall, 1973; UA012.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Bray Lab
  - BLDGS, 1989; UA012.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Capen House - Africana center
  - Buildings (exterior), 1973 -- 1990; UA012.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Tufts buildings
  - Buildings (exterior), 1990; UA012.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Olin, Classroom, West Hall. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1980; UA012.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou, Chapel, arial. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1975; UA012.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou, labratory, Academic quad, Memorial Steps. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Chapel, West Hall, Frat Row, view from Ballou Window. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1965; UA012.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Chapel, Ballou, Barnum Museum. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1965; UA012.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Memorial steps, Ballou, Barnum Museum. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Memorial steps, old bookstore and others. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Library, old bookstore, Packard. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of old bookstore, Packard. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of side gates and Packard. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of ROTC building, Miller Hall, old library, academic quad. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Hodgdon, Eaton, Miller. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1970; UA012.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Dewick Hall, Anderson-Robinson, academic quad. Date is approximate
  - Buildings (exterior), 1990; UA012.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
    This folder contains negatives of Ballou, Campus center, International Research center. Date is approximate
  - Bush, Dewick, Haskell, 1970; UA012.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Bush, Dewick, Haskell. Date is approximate
  - Bush, Dewick, Hodgdon, 1970; UA012.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
    This folder contains slides of Bush, Dewick, Hodgdon. Date is approximate
  - Campus slides [Ballou], 1960; UA012.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Campus slides [Ballou], 1960; UA012.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Campus slides [Ballou], 1960; UA012.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Campus slides [Ballou], 1960; UA012.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Campus slides [Chapel], 1973; UA012.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Goddard Chapel.
  - Campus slides [Chapel], 1970; UA012.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Goddard Chapel. Date is approximate
  - Campus slides [Chapel], 1970; UA012.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Campus slides [Chapel], 1965; UA012.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    This folder contains photos of Tufts campus. Date is approximate
  - Carmichael, 1960; UA012.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of charmichael exterior. Date is approximate
  - Carmichael, 1960; UA012.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Carmichael- Gayer Gate, 1960; UA012.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Carmichael- Miller, 1973; UA012.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Charmichael and Miller exterior.
  - Carmichael- Miller, 1961; UA012.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Cousens Gym, 1961 -- 1975; UA012.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Cousens Gym.
  - Cousens Gym, 1980; UA012.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Cousens Gym and Gantcher center rendering. Date is approximate
  - Dewick -MacPhie, 1960; UA012.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides Dewick - MacPhie. Date is approximate
  - Dewick -MacPhie, 1990; UA012.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Dowling Hall, 1990; UA012.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Dowling Hall. Date is approximate
  - Dowling Hall, 1990; UA012.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - East Hall, 1990; UA012.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of East Hall. Date is approximate
  - East Hall, 1987 -- 1993; UA012.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of East Hall.
  - Eaton Library, 1985; UA012.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Eaton. Date is approximate
  - Eaton Library, 1970 -- 1990; UA012.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Ballou, Pearson, construction of Miller, plaque, classroom scenes. Date is approximate
  - Eaton Library, 1970 -- 1990; UA012.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Bowen gate, dorm room, classroom scenes. Date is approximate
  - Eaton Library, 1960; UA012.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Eaton Library, 1960; UA012.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Eaton Library Interior, 1957; UA012.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Eaton's interior.
  - Eaton Library Interior, 1957; UA012.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Eaton Library Interior, 1957; UA012.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Eaton Library Interior, 1957; UA012.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Eaton War Memorial, 1970; UA012.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Eaton's exterior. Date is approximate
  - Eaton War Memorial, 1970; UA012.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Eliot Pearson, 1975; UA012.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior/playground of Eliot Pearson. Date is approximate
  - Fischer Arcade, 2009; UA012.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Tufts Campus. Date as marked
  - Fletcher, 1970; UA012.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Fletcher and Dean Hall. Date is approximate
  - Foliage, 1991; UA012.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of green foliage.
  - Goddard, Jumbo, Anderson, 2009; UA012.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Goddard Chapel, Jumbo, Anderson/Memorial Steps, President's house. Date as marked
  - Gravity Stone, 1985; UA012.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the Gravity Stone. Date is approximate
  - Halligan, 1990; UA012.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Halligan. Date is approximate
  - Halligan/Engineering, 1990; UA012.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Halligan's interior w/ students. Date is approximate
  - Hillsides, 1970; UA012.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of Hillsides. Date is approximate
  - Hodgdon, 1960; UA012.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Hodgdon. Date is approximate
  - Hodgdon, 1960 -- 1973; UA012.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Hodgdon and campus road (1973). Date is approximate
  - Hodgdon and Sweet, 1960; UA012.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Hodgdon Sweet Hall (ROTC). Date is approximate
  - Lane Hall and Boiler Plant, 1965; UA012.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Lane Hall and Boiler Plant. Date is approximate
  - Latin Way, 1970; UA012.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior and construction of Latin Way. Date is approximate
  - Lerner-Medford Campus, 1987 -- 1989; UA012.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the Lerner and Memorial Steps.
  - Library, 1980; UA012.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of the Library. Date is approximate
  - Lincoln-Filene Center, UA012.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the Lincoln-Filene Center.
  - Mayer Campus Ctr, 1985; UA012.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mayer Campus Center.
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1986; UA012.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior and dining of Mayer Campus Center.
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1985; UA012.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mayer Campus Center and Campus scenes. Date is approximate
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1986; UA012.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mayer Campus Center
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1990; UA012.001.003.00054 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mayer Campus Center. Date is approximate
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1970; UA012.001.003.00055 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mayer Campus Center and renderings. Date is approximate
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1985 -- 1986; UA012.001.003.00056 (Box 3)
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1985 -- 1986; UA012.001.003.00057 (Box 3)
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1986; UA012.001.003.00058 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior and dining of Mayer Campus Center
  - Mayer Campus Center, 1985; UA012.001.003.00059 (Box 3)
    This folder contains slides of the exterior of Mayer Campus Center with students. Date is approximate
  - Medford Campus, 1970; UA012.001.004.00001 (Box 4)